<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
        <title>Hack ID</title>
        <description>Hack ID - K. Anthony</description>
        <link>http://hackid.github.io</link>
        <atom:link href="http://hackid.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 23:49:17 -0600</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 23:49:17 -0600</pubDate>
        <ttl>60</ttl>


        <item>
                <title>Writing Tips to Grab Your Learners' Attention and Keep it!</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;On-screen text can be a powerful tool to motivate, inspire, entertain, and educate. Instructional designers can use many tools to help make onscreen text Meaningful, Memorable, and Motivational.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This e-book, perfect for all instructional designers, outlines 5 practical writing tips that can be used to grab learner attention and keep it!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/writing-tips-attention</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/writing-tips-attention</guid>
                <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Avoiding Ugly e-Learning: Lessons from Holiday Sweaters</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;Tis the season of holiday sweaters—each lovingly created with good intent, sometimes gaudy, sometimes uncomfortable, sometimes utilitarian, but rarely as beautiful as imagined. The same can often be said about e-learning course designs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We start out with the intention to create something uniquely satisfying for our learners, but after accounting for strained resources, limited time, imperfect development tools, complex subject matter, and unpredictable learners, we end up with something not quite as beautiful as we’d hoped.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/ugly-sweater-lessons</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/ugly-sweater-lessons</guid>
                <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>10 Practical Principles for Creating Impactful e-Learning</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;Instructional designers of e-learning face a constant challenge of how to create learning experiences that actually make a difference. Too many of the accepted and easy approaches result in e-learning courses that fail to motivate, engage, or empower learners. Sophisticated simulations and technically-sophisticated designs seem out of reach for many instructional designers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this e-book, learn:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;10 practical principles that should be implemented at any level of complexity to create training experiences that are transforming and memorable.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Actionable tips to implement these principles into your e-learning designs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/principles-for-impactful-elearning</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/principles-for-impactful-elearning</guid>
                <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>7 Steps To Improved E-Learning Challenges</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;The Context, Challenge, Activity, and Feedback (CCAF) Instructional Design Model is a powerful tool to guide the design of engaging and effective online interactions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instructional designers appreciate the power of these elements and are impressed when presented with finished interactions that exemplify these principles. However, when faced with designing an interaction from scratch, many designers find it difficult to break out of the traditional tedious multiple choice and true/false formats that are used so often.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This e-book provides seven small steps to improved interactions while recognizing that capabilities with authoring software might be quite limited. If you begin applying these steps while you are designing questions, you will quickly open up a world of much more powerful design possibilities.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/improved-elearning-challenges</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/improved-elearning-challenges</guid>
                <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>A Bite-Sized Guide to Microlearning</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;You have heard the buzz and excitement in the learning industry about microlearning—but how do you put the principles and theories behind microlearning into action?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Explore the basics of microlearning design and get foundational knowledge on implementing microlearning at your organization!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This e-book delivers insights into what makes successful microlearning gleaned from Ellen’s experience working with varied companies and organizations.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/bitesize-microlearning</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/bitesize-microlearning</guid>
                <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>14 Tips for Preparing an e-Learning Feast</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;As we all get ready to join our family and friends for the Thanksgiving holidays and prepare for the big meal, it’s nearly impossible to avoid the endless advice on TV, radio, and online about how to prepare the perfect feast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As it turns out, so much of that advice can easily be related to planning and preparing perfect e-learning.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/14-tips-elearning-feast</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/14-tips-elearning-feast</guid>
                <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>


</channel>
</rss>
