<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
        <title>Hack ID</title>
        <description>Hack ID - K. Anthony</description>
        <link>http://hackid.github.io</link>
        <atom:link href="http://hackid.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 02:14:26 -0600</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 02:14:26 -0600</pubDate>
        <ttl>60</ttl>


        <item>
                <title>Free Code Camp</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;Free Code Camp is a friendly open source community where you learn to code and help nonprofits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We help our campers build job-worthy portfolios of real apps used by real people, while helping nonprofits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You start by working through our self-paced, browser-based full stack JavaScript curriculum. By working through our curriculum, you can earn four certifications:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Front End Certification&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Data Visualization Certification&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Back End Certification&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Full Stack Certification&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/free-code-camp</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/free-code-camp</guid>
                <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Devices Everywhere: Designing for a Multi-Device World</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;People today use multiple connected devices—PCs, smartphones, tablets, TVs, and beyond—switching between them, and using them together in order to accomplish a single goal. Still, most products merely replicate the same experience across devices, substituting solos for what could be an orchestra. In this session, I’d like to introduce ‘The 3C’s”- an ecosystem approach for designing multi-device experiences, one that focuses on context.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/devices-everywhere</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/devices-everywhere</guid>
                <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>xAPI Learning Cohort</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;Join us for another dive into xAPI and what you can do to make it work for you, your organization, and the entire industry!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No xAPI experience necessary. Lots of friendly, curious folks. Real, live projects with real, live products. Virtual meetings so anyone in the world can participate. It’s all plus with no minus!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/xapi-learning-cohort</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/xapi-learning-cohort</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>xAPI: An Introductory Guide</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;Consider this introductory e-book a crash course – everything you’ll need to know to have a basic understanding of the Experience API™, otherwise known as xAPI. xAPI is an open data interoperability specification originally developed to get a better picture of how, when, and why learning happens both on and offline.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/xapi-intro-guide</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/xapi-intro-guide</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>The Essential Guide to Working with Subject Matter Experts</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;If you’re like most e-learning developers, working with subject matter experts (SMEs) is one of your toughest challenges. But don’t worry, we’re here to help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Download this e-book to learn effective strategies for partnering with your SMEs to create awesome e-learning. You’ll learn how to get the information and feedback that you need—and how to make collaborating on courses a positive experience for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/working-with-smes</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/working-with-smes</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>The Fundamentals Of User Experience</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;Change the way you think and look at products (digital and otherwise) forever. Learn what user experience is and how it affects every decision you and your users will ever make.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/ux-fundamentals</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/ux-fundamentals</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Unity Programming for Human Beings</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;We are stoked to announce the launch of our free ebook Unity Programming for Human Beings, authored by software engineer and game developer Jesse Glove, in collaboration with Pablo Farias Navarro, founder of Zenva.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In over 230 pages of awesomeness, the book starts from zero and covers all the way to building simple 2D and 3D games with Unity.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/unity-for-humans</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/unity-for-humans</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>How to Use Typography to Improve Your E-Learning</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;Typography—or the art of creating characters for print—is a powerful tool for setting the right mood and tone for your e-learning course. Choosing the right typefaces will help you create clear, beautiful, and legible text that complements the content, interactions, and graphics in your course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this rich guide to typography for e-learning designers, we’ll show you how to create a professional, elegant look for your course by choosing the right typefaces.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/typography-improve-elearning</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/typography-improve-elearning</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Sponge UK Elearning Podcast</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;Getting to the heart of great elearning with absorbing interviews, ideas, and tips. The perfect show for L&amp;amp;D professionals, instructional designers, and anyone interested in digital learning. We cover the technology behind learning, as well as the theory and practice that goes into absorbing online learning.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/sponge-uk-podcast</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/sponge-uk-podcast</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>The Secret to Create Great E-Learning Videos</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;Videos let you show a learner what they need to know, not just tell them. And for soft-skills training, they’re invaluable for capturing the subtleties of personal interactions. In this e-book, we’ll share our expert tips on creating compelling videos and screencasts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn how to set up a professional-quality studio with simple, affordable equipment, including lighting you can find at your local hardware store. Get tips for speaking or narrating with a natural, authentic tone. Save time by effectively preparing your desktop for screen recordings. Enhance your videos with captions and interactions to make sure they communicate key points.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/secret-elearning-videos</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/secret-elearning-videos</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Sales: Blended Learning That Works</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;Helping organisations improve the sales and product knowledge training they deliver, focusing in increasing ROI and sales performance through blended learning.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/sales-learning-that-works</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/sales-learning-that-works</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>A Rough Guide to Multi-device</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;If your training needs to be delivered to a wide audience, or could last beyond the life of your current desktop or laptop systems then it could benefit from a multi-device approach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this guide we’ll give you the information you need to make an informed decision about the right option for your learning approach.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/rough-guide-multidevice</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/rough-guide-multidevice</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>A Rough Guide to Interactive Video</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;Employees expect more than ever before from their digital learning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interactive video is a way to transform workplace learning into a creative and effective experience, but it is still a relatively new kid on the block. Find out how interactive video training can make a real difference in your organisation with our complimentary handbook, A Rough Guide to Interactive video.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/rough-guide-interactive-video</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/rough-guide-interactive-video</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>A Rough Guide to Induction</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;The first day of a new job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a pivotal moment for both new employee and employer, but without the right induction or onboarding this new working relationship could be short-lived.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Businesses with effective induction training have a 50% higher retention rate of new staff, as well as improved employee engagement and productivity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find out how elearning can help your organisation deliver a high quality, consistent induction experience with our complimentary handbook, A rough guide to induction.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/rough-guide-induction</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/rough-guide-induction</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>A Rough Guide to Games</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;Games are gaining ground in workplace elearning with an estimated 40% of global organisations already using them in some shape or form. Learn more about what makes a good elearning game and why you should be using games in your elearning.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/rough-guide-games</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/rough-guide-games</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>How To Shoot Rich Cultural Training Videos on a Smartphone (A Guide)</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;The value of creating rich, engaging cultural stories using video is often outweighed by the perceived time, expertise and outside resources needed to produce these videos. Especially in the L&amp;amp;D world, where video creation is one area where content creators and instructional designers don’t feel as comfortable giving it a shot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this guide, we will take you step-by-step through the proven Wisetail video production process from a filmmaking novice’s point of view. We’ll give you both the insight and techniques needed to tell your rich cultural stories using the tools (smartphone &amp;amp; laptop) already at your disposal.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/rich-cultural-video</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/rich-cultural-video</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Responsive eLearning Design &amp; Development</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;Today’s learners use multiple computing/communication devices during the course of the day - for learning, work, entertainment, and decision making. They are on the move, both within and outside the workplace, and want to use their “downtime” effectively. Responsive eLearning helps organizations to leverage this “downtime” while extending the reach and availability of their training.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like any other approach, Responsive eLearning comes with its own set of planning, design, development and testing considerations and guidelines - and it forces those of us who create responsive eLearning to think beyond just one fixed display size and one uniform use context. Hence, understanding the key features, benefits, types, examples of Responsive eLearning is important in drawing up a strategy that works for your organization. With respect to the strategy, decision factors like when to use responsive eLearning, how to get started and the various challenges you may encounter in the design, development and testing process are crucial to the success of your strategy. Learn about it all in this eBook.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/responsive-design-development</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/responsive-design-development</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Resonate Multi-Touch Book</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;Resonate Multi-Touch Book is like having a portable story writing workshop in your hands as you prepare your next presentation. You’ll learn a new presentation development methodology informed by cinema, literature, and the greatest speeches of all time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/resonate-multi-touch</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/resonate-multi-touch</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Ready, Set, Curate!</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;Let’s face it, the internet isn’t getting any smaller. How do we separate the valuable content from the noise, how do we organise the good stuff in ways that tell coherent stories about our businesses and our interests? In this latest offering from HT2 you’ll be able to inform your own practice by taking a look at ‘Curation’ and answering these questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is it (and why do we need it)?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What are the ‘pros’ &amp;amp; ‘cons’?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What do I need to think about before I get started?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What tools are available for me to use?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/ready-set-curate</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/ready-set-curate</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Product Psychology</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;This content is designed for people who want to know the deeper reasons behind why people do what they do. This is for the busy entrepreneur, designer, or marketer who wants to know techniques they can use to help build better products and ultimately improve people’s lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve asked our friends and colleagues for their top three to five resources on important topics related to product psychology and user behavior. They’ve taken the time to dig up their favorite articles, videos, and resources to get you up to speed quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>http://hackid.github.io/product-psychology</link>
                <guid>http://hackid.github.io/product-psychology</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>


</channel>
</rss>
